koinup.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Koinup

## The Introduction

Koinup recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use the website [koinup.com](http://www.koinup.com/) or other web sites owned or operated by Koinup S.r.l. value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Koinup Sites. Koinup provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Koinup and related web Sites.   
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Koinup [Terms of Use](http://www.koinup.com/support/terms-of-use/). Your use of the Koinup Sites and any personal information you provide on the Koinup Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](http://www.koinup.com/support/terms-of-use/). 

The use of private information provided by user to Koinup is subject to the italian Legislative Decree d.lgs 196/2003. 

Please note that any video, image, storyboard, text, comment, url or other content posted as user submission (to see what is user submission read our [Terms of Use](http://www.koinup.com/support/terms-of-use/)) onto the Koinup Sites becomes a "published and public" content and is not considered an information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

##  Informations collected by Koinup

  * **User Provided Information** : You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Koinup when choosing to participate in various activities on the Koinup Sites such as uploading contents, posting comments, subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists, etc. These informations are required to access all the features of the website. To access Koinup features you don't have to provide us sensible and legal private-identifiable informations (ethnical, religious, economical, political informations, etc).
  * **Cookies Information** : When you visit the Koinup Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Koinup uses both session cookies and persistent cookies . A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Koinup Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  * **Log File Information** : When you use the Koinup Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

##  The Way Koinup Uses Information

The Koinup use and/or disclosure of your private information is subjected to the italian legislative decree d.lgs. 196/2003.   
The following are the way we assume to uses the user's information we collect:

a) We can use your personal identifiable and/or not identifiable information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Koinup Sites. 

b) Privacy Policy doesn't apply to the Contents you uploaded and published on Koinup. 

c) We can use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality of the Koinup Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. We also use non identifiable and impersonale informations to promote and advertise the website or to create stats about the website, their users and their behavior. 

d) We can provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses which work for Koinup and its website on legal, marketing, tecnological issues with the purpose to improve the quality of the website or remove bugs, technological problem and other stuff related to the maintenance and development of Koinup. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures 

e) We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or if it is necessary to comply with italian laws or respond to a court order.

With the exception of the points discussed above (mainly the points _a), c), d), e)_ ) Koinup won't never disclosure your private identifiable informations in any occasion and for any reason. Koinup commits itself to mantain and assure the security of your private identifiable and not-identifiable personale informations 

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Koinup Sites, in which case Koinup may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

## Advertising on Koinup

  * Koinup strives to provide you with relevant and useful advertising and we use the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx), as well as other third party ad serving systems, to do so. We may use a range of information including cookies, web beacons, IP addresses, usage data and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as browser type and operating system) to provide you with relevant advertising. If you are logged into your Koinup Account, we may also show you advertising based on the information you have provided to us in your Koinup Account.
  * We use the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) on Koinup to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on this site and other Google and AdSense partner websites. Advertisers may serve ads based on interests associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, frequency of uploading or activity on other AdSense partner sites. Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser's website. This non-personally identifiable information is held separately from your Koinup Account data, or other personally identifying information in our possession.
  * You may view, edit and add to the categories used to provide you with interest-based advertising in the [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences?hl=en-US) for the DoubleClick cookie. Your ads preferences will be respected across Koinup, AdSense partner sites and Google sites using the DoubleClick cookie to serve such ads. For more information about interest-based advertising and the Ads Preference Manager [see FAQ](http://www.google.com/privacy_faq.html).
  * You also may choose to [opt out of the DoubleClick cookie](http://optout.doubleclick.com/cgi-bin/optoutgoogle.pl) at any time. If you select the DoubleClick opt-out cookie, ads delivered to your browser by our ad-serving technology will not be served based on the DoubleClick cookie. Find more information [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_faq.html) about opting out of the DoubleClick cookie.
  * Other third-party ad serving companies or networks may display ads on Koinup. Koinup does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Koinup's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Koinup is maintained and dealt with by Koinup in accordance with this privacy policy. 

##  Rights of the customer 

The processing owner of the personal data is Koinup (Koinup S.r.l., Via Romanino 12, 25122 Brescia - Italy) and specifically its Personnel and Organization Manager. 

You can contact him via email at [privacy@koinup.com](mailto:privacy@koinup.com) or sending a phisical comunication at Koinup S.r.l., Via Romanino 12, 25122 Brescia - Italy) 

Users may always appeal to the Processing Manager (see above contact info) to assert their rights as set out in Art. 7 of Legislative Decree 196/03, which states the following: 

1\. The interested party has the right to obtain confirmation of the existence, or not, of personal details that regard him/her, even if not yet registered, and the communication thereof in an intelligible form. 

2\. The interested party has the right to obtain evidence of:   
a. the origin of the personal details;   
b. the purpose and manner of processing;   
c. the logic applied in case of processing effected with the aid of electronic tools;   
d. the identity details of the owner, manager and agent designate as set out in Art. 5 clause 2;   
e.the subjects and categories to which the data may be communicated or who might come to know of it in the role of designated national representative, manager or person in charge. 

3\. The interested party has the right to obtain:   
a. the update, correction or, when necessary, completion of data;   
b. the cancellation, transformation to anonymity or blocking of data processed in violation of the law, including that whose conservation is unnecessary in relation to the purpose for which the data was, or will be, subsequently processed; c. the declaration that the operations set out in letters a) and b) above, also as regards their content, have been brought to the notice of those to whom the data was communicated or disseminated, excepting those cases in which this is impossible or would require a manifestly disproportionate use of resources with respect to the right being protected. 

4\. The interested party has the right to object, in whole or in part, to:   
a. the processing of personal data that regards him/her, for legitimate motives, even though pertinent to the purpose of their collection;   
b. the processing of personal data that regards him/her for the purpose of sending publicity material or direct selling, for carrying out market research or sending commercial messages. 

##  Our Commitment To Data Security 

Koinup uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Koinup and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Koinup makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. 

If Koinup learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Koinup may post a notice on the Koinup Sites if a security breach occurs. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy when it will be necessary. Take care to check periodically this Privacy Policy to see if any updates will be featured. 

Last modified: March 13, 2009
